Basketball Pro Julius van Sauers experienced racist abuse when he first moved to play in the UK
We moved to Glasgow, me and my teammates...
into one apartment,
and our neighbours below...
They just started complaining...
about... y'know, us
slamming doors and having parties and
y'know, stomping, and jumping up and down.
So, they came down and knocked on the door a few times,
so yeah, we talked it out and everything,
just like regular neighbours and
after that, they called the cops on us...
for y'know, noise complaints and stuff,
and from there, it actually escalated...
There were so many complaints, people were calling our team...
that we were bringing prostitutes and not cleaning up our trash,
and it felt like the whole neighbourhood was watching us.
And... we had...
at one point our cars were- the tyres were slashed,
and it escalated into our cars being damaged...
the windows being smashed and everything.