Basketball Pro Julius van Sauers experienced racist abuse when he first moved to play in the UK
At the time, I,
I just felt like they were,
honestly, just annoying neighbours. I felt like oh, we, y'know,
we got a bad one, which is unlucky...
Y'know, I didn't think they had any racial...
motives or anything...
But once our tyres got slashed, we were
just a little suspicious that
something more might be going on.
Y'know, we had like four
flat tyres in like two weeks,
that couldn't be any coincidence...
So at the time, when that happened, I felt a little bit
unsure and unsafe.
But before that, felt pretty-
we felt good, we were happy to be there and
everything, y'know, we were happy with our scene,
and happy for everyone...
to have us in Glasgow.