Basketball Pro Julius van Sauers experienced racist abuse when he first moved to play in the UK
Well, our team, they had those calls...
and when the neighbours called up they said, y'know,
something along the lines of, "Get those black b******s outta here."
and they were, at first, our team,
they were just like, "Hey, keep it down and y'know, respect the neighbours."
And we're like, "We are," and then- at one point, they believed us, y'know, that
this was getting outrageous, it was getting crazy...
Y'know, when you get the cops calling on you, where you're alone at home...
That's just crazy.
So, our team just supported us, big time...
They made sure that we had everything that we needed,
and... when we moved,
they made quick arrangements for us, y'know, to make sure that we were safe...
and that we were comfortable to keep playing basketball.
So they took good care of us, they,
they handled everything with the police and everything so,
that was pretty good.