Basketball Pro Julius van Sauers experienced racist abuse when he first moved to play in the UK
I think a big,
a big step forward probably would be,
just to understand and,
have sympathy for the situation,
and actually think a lot of people did that.
I've had so many.. so many messages and
y'know, people reaching out to us...
Y'know, supporting us,
that was already- that was amazing...
I think racism will never really go away...
So I think it's just very important to be strong as a community,
and- not let it, y'know, come through, y'know what I mean?..
Do not let outsiders come in and
start any racism.
I think it's very important to be strong as a community,
and have rules and guidelines and...
that- I think that would be a great start.