Basketball Pro Julius van Sauers experienced racist abuse when he first moved to play in the UK
I would say for anyone who would
suffer the same as me or my teammates...
We actually- I think we handled it pretty well...
by just doing what we had to do...
Y'know, it's not easy but I think it's-
we try to surround ourselves with people that
were supporting us, y'know, like I just said...
I think it's a bad idea to stay alone and
fight the situation, I think,
y'know, fighting fire with fire does not make any sense.
So, supportive to them,
to stay with your community, with people that love you and support you,
and.. I think that's the most important part.