Carol was diagnosed with bowel cancer 16 years ago
There's a good resource now on Bowel Cancer UK website,
there's a little diary that you can- you can download.
I didn't have it in my day, I don't even know if I kept notes, but
I would certainly recommend that, that anyone that's worried,
and feels that their symptoms are ongoing,
and nothing seems to be happening to them,
I would certainly keep a diary and keep pursuing,
you know, keep pursuing it.
And, actually earlier on, as well, I think I would have asked
to see a different doctor, because I was seeing
the same one throughout, so I would recommend that as well.
But don't give up, because, you know,
if you- if you do feel there's something wrong,
it's your body, you know it better than anybody else, and you know,
I would recommend that you just pursue that.