Carol was diagnosed with bowel cancer 16 years ago
I think I'm pretty positive as people go anyway,
I try to think positive, think about, you know, positive things.
I found it- I like walking a lot, but I found that
the chemotherapy actually zaps your energy.
And you know, you really aren't one for,
you know, if you're going through
that kind of treatment, you're not- not really ready to go out
and- and, you know, do a 5 mile hike or whatever.
So that would be, you know, the first thing
that I would think about, but I don't think that's always possible.
So I think you just got to think of positive thoughts and,
you know, friends and family keep you positive as well.