Carol was diagnosed with bowel cancer 16 years ago
Well, I think there are a list of symptoms.
I think most people say that if you've got-
if you find blood in your poo, then that's,
you know, that's the first thing.
The first thing you should do really is go to your GP.
I didn't have that symptom, I just had this- this pain in my side
that just went on and on and on.
But unfortunately, as I said, I had a bit of a bad experience,
and I wasn't really, the diagnosis wasn't
picked up really for, as I said, 18 months and I saw different
doctor in the end, luckily, and he sent me
immediately for treatment to A&E,
and I had a scan and an X-ray,
and that's really when things started to happen.