David Needham was diagnosed with Motor Neurone Disease in 2014 which had a major impact on his mental and physical health.
He is the Secretary of the Leicester Tigers Wheelchair Rugby Club and also gets involved in coaching.
It's hard for me
to actually put my finger on
exactly when my love for sport started,
but it was a very young age.
I've got vague recollections
of going to watch my dad
and my uncle playing
in representative matches at cricket.
And I think it was then that it got my goat,
it really got a hold of me.
But it wasn't until sort of, several years later
where I could actually start
picking a ball up and playing myself that
it really took hold...
Very, very young age; five, six, seven.