David Needham was diagnosed with Motor Neurone Disease in 2014 which had a major impact on his mental and physical health.
He is the Secretary of the Leicester Tigers Wheelchair Rugby Club and also gets involved in coaching.
It was a very long
and drawn out experience,
that- that sounds terrible,
but in a- in a perverse way,
very much worked for me, in that
I figured it out for myself
before I received the diagnosis.
I was in the medical system about
two and three quarter years,
going backwards and forwards,
getting asked the same questions
over and over again,
and not really getting anywhere.
I did my research,
I'd got a good idea of what it was about...
I asked to be referred
to an MND specialist,
up in Sheffield,
fully expecting to be told
that there was not a chance of that.
And about three months after that,
I went into hospital,
for a couple of days,
had to endure a lot of tests,
and then a fortnight later, got a call
to go back up to Sheffield,
and we had the news broken to us,
and like I said, it came as no shock to me.