David Needham was diagnosed with Motor Neurone Disease in 2014 which had a major impact on his mental and physical health.
He is the Secretary of the Leicester Tigers Wheelchair Rugby Club and also gets involved in coaching.
The support- I mean,
one of the biggest places
that I found support in, well there were two.
The Motor Neuron Disease Association
have been absolutely fantastic,
can't knock them at all.
They're constantly, sort of
knocking on the door
saying, "You know, if anything
you need, y'know, we're there," and reminding me.
But the best place that I found
support was going back
into the sporting environment.
Joining the Leicester Tigers Wheelchair Rugby Club,
and getting involved
with Matt Hampson Foundation.
The support there has been
absolutely fantastic.