David Needham was diagnosed with Motor Neurone Disease in 2014 which had a major impact on his mental and physical health.
He is the Secretary of the Leicester Tigers Wheelchair Rugby Club and also gets involved in coaching.
That was my wife,
as it turns out, she...
she realised before me that,
me stepping back from sport
was completely the wrong thing for me.
And she went and knocked on the door
of DMU Leisure Centre,
which is on our beat, and asked the question,
you know, would I be made welcome
in the wheelchair rugby club?
And the guys were great, got me straight in,
in straight in a chair,
and from the first time I sat in it,
and had a blast at the
game, I was hooked.