David Needham was diagnosed with Motor Neurone Disease in 2014 which had a major impact on his mental and physical health.
He is the Secretary of the Leicester Tigers Wheelchair Rugby Club and also gets involved in coaching.
The one that stands out
for me and it's huge,
and I wish I could go back
and relive that,
sort of part of my life.
When I was getting towards the end of
my time playing able bodied sports,
and picking up injuries,
left, right, centre - that
was down to MND as it turned out.
I interpreted it as just my body saying,
"Enough's enough.
You've had 39 great years,
now knock it on the head,
go and find something different to do."
That was a huge mistake.
That effectively opened the door
for MND to come in and take hold.
While I've been active,
I've been very conscious
that the MND's progression
has been very slow.
When I'm inactive,
it seems to catch up with me
an awful lot quicker.
So, the two years that I spent
not playing sports,
I would not do that again.